Guide to the George Rosen Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Personal Papers and Photographs, 1930-1977; Series VI
  - Clippings, 1956-1977 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Curriculum vitae, Circa 1976 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Diplomas and certificates, 1935-1969 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Elisabeth Severance Prentiss National Award in Health Education, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Letters of condolence, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Memorabilia, 1936-1977, undated (Box 37, Folder 8-9)
    See also: Oversize, folder 2
  - Military record, 1946, 1969 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Photographs
    - George Rosen and Beate Caspari-Rosen, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - George Rosen with groups, 1938-1939, 1958, undated (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - American Public Health Association Annual Conferences, 1928-1937 (Box 37, Folder 13-25)
    - American Public Health Association delegation to Mexico City
      See: Oversize, folder 1
  - University of Berlin, 1931-1934, undated (Box 37, Folder 26)
- Oversize, 1930-1977
  - American Public Health Association [photographs of 1930 delegation to Mexico City] (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Memorabilia, 1963, undated (Box 38, Folder 2)